<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>eitherway - A Story to my Start-Up on eitherway</title>
    <link>https://eitherway.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in eitherway - A Story to my Start-Up on eitherway</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 18:53:21 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://eitherway.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>You Are Planning Too Much</title>
      <link>https://eitherway.io/posts/you-are-planning-too-much/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 11:45:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eitherway.io/posts/you-are-planning-too-much/</guid>
      <description>You are planning too much  Fri, Sep 11, 2020
 Or at least this is one of the things I realized myself. Why do I say that? I&amp;rsquo;ve built a project and I invested quite some time into it. I planned how to deploy it, how to market it, and how to launch it. But after some customer conversation, I realized: It will most likely fail. So all these plans will not actually help me anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tipps to Code more secure Web-Apps</title>
      <link>https://eitherway.io/posts/tipps-secure-webapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 15:46:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eitherway.io/posts/tipps-secure-webapp/</guid>
      <description>Tipps to Code more secure Web-Apps  Mon, Aug 24, 2020
 Disclaimer: I am not a security expert.
This post is a collection of quick tiny little things that could improve your security drastically. We would have a much safer web if more developers would know some of these resources and tips.
Use a checklist This might sound a bit weird, but checklists are a great and powerful tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack your Mind: Remember Everything</title>
      <link>https://eitherway.io/guide/remember-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 15:42:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eitherway.io/guide/remember-everything/</guid>
      <description>Hack your Mind: Remember Everything  Mon, May 11, 2020
 helicopter, electric range, Newfoundland, albino, retrovirus, wheelbarrow, battery, tractor, fox, hypotenuse, slender, elm, stone, harmony, lint, banana, ladder
It took me 40 seconds to remember this sequence and I could repeat it months after I learned it. It&amp;rsquo;s from an episode of &amp;ldquo;The Mentalist&amp;rdquo; (Season 7 Episode 3 at 10:10). It showed me the real power of a technique called &amp;ldquo;Memory Palace&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I created this blog</title>
      <link>https://eitherway.io/story/how-i-created-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 22:30:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eitherway.io/story/how-i-created-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>How I created this blog  Fri, Apr 24, 2020
 I wanted to write a blog about my start-up story. For that I needed a blog. This is the story of its creation. From it&amp;rsquo;s name, to the design, to the implementation. The concepts and tools I used included.
01 Why I created this blog?   Make personal goals public to achieve them
  Create inspiring blog articles for others</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://eitherway.io/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 22:08:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eitherway.io/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy  effective Thu, Aug 27, 2020
 I (&amp;ldquo;Eitherway&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;me&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;my&amp;rdquo;) am responsible for the data processing.
This privacy policy applies to all information collected through my websites (such as eitherway.io).
The short version I am using Simple Analytics as a way to see some statistics about my blog. However they don&amp;rsquo;t store or collect any personal data from you. For more information on what Simple Analytics collects (or mostly what they don&amp;rsquo;t collect) click here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imprint</title>
      <link>https://eitherway.io/imprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 22:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eitherway.io/imprint/</guid>
      <description>Imprint   Website Owner and Person responsible for the content according to § 55 RStV Ramon Reschke
Paul-Lincke-Straße 18
66113 Saarbrücken
E-Mail: hostmaster@eitherway.io
Phone: 015678 316796
All the contact information of me given on this website including any photos are explicitly for information purposes or to contact me.
They shall not be used for sending advertisements, spam or the like.
Should this information nevertheless be used for the above-mentioned purposes, I reserve the right to take legal action.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>