<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on eitherway</title>
    <link>https://eitherway.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on eitherway</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 13:18:56 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://eitherway.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Build a Raspberry Pi NAS they said. It will be easy...</title>
      <link>https://eitherway.io/posts/raspberry-pi-nas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 13:18:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eitherway.io/posts/raspberry-pi-nas/</guid>
      <description>Build a Raspberry Pi NAS they said. It will be easy...  * Nobody said that, I had the idea myself.
 First off, what were the goals? The NAS should be:
 redundant and protect from a drive failure. cheap. an easy to use solution for my onsite backup. powered by a single USB-C Cable.  Just connect two SSDs via USB to a Raspberry Pi 4 and run the NAS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching an E-Book for malicious code with VIM</title>
      <link>https://eitherway.io/posts/epub-malicious-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 15:46:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eitherway.io/posts/epub-malicious-code/</guid>
      <description>Searching an E-Book for malicious code with VIM  Mon, Nov 30, 2020
 I recently received a rather suspicious E-Book in epub format. Like PDFs, these can also contain malicious code. I wanted to open it, but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if I could trust it.
In the past, I would have deleted it straight away. But this time I wanted to actually know if there is malicious code inside this file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Are Planning Too Much</title>
      <link>https://eitherway.io/posts/you-are-planning-too-much/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 11:45:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eitherway.io/posts/you-are-planning-too-much/</guid>
      <description>You are planning too much  Fri, Sep 11, 2020
 Or at least this is one of the things I realized myself. Why do I say that? I&amp;rsquo;ve built a project and I invested quite some time into it. I planned how to deploy it, how to market it, and how to launch it. But after some customer conversation, I realized: It will most likely fail. So all these plans will not actually help me anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tipps to Code more secure Web-Apps</title>
      <link>https://eitherway.io/posts/tipps-secure-webapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 15:46:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eitherway.io/posts/tipps-secure-webapp/</guid>
      <description>Tipps to Code more secure Web-Apps  Mon, Aug 24, 2020
 Disclaimer: I am not a security expert.
This post is a collection of quick tiny little things that could improve your security drastically. We would have a much safer web if more developers would know some of these resources and tips.
Use a checklist This might sound a bit weird, but checklists are a great and powerful tool.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
